[
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Why Burger King sponsored Stevenage F.C.",
    "sUrl": "https://www.stevenagefc.com/",
    "sText": "Burger King",
    "tFront": "Viral",
    "tBack": "viral",
    "slug": "stevenage-challenge",
    "img": "stevenage",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "You have to admire Burger King's creativity. For the 19/20 football season they sponsored Stevenage F.C. all to get their logo in FIFA 20. They then offered rewards for gamers to play as Stevenage, score goals, and share on Twitter."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "£8k Instagram Giveaway → 1M followers",
    "sUrl": "https://www.instagram.com/mollymaehague/",
    "sText": "Molly-Mae",
    "tFront": "Giveaway",
    "tBack": "giveaway",
    "slug": "molly-mae",
    "img": "molly",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Last week Molly-Mae did an Instagram giveaway. She spent £8k on gifts. Her reward was 1M new followers and subscribers across Instagram and YouTube. That's < 1p / new fan. Possibly the best ROI I've seen. Let's break it down."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "The marketing genius of Andrew Schulz",
    "sUrl": "https://theandrewschulz.com/",
    "sText": "Andrew Schulz",
    "tFront": "Viral",
    "tBack": "viral",
    "slug": "andrew-schulz",
    "img": "schulz",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Let’s start in 2017. Andrew Schulz had been killing it in the New York comedy clubs for over a decade. But no network would give him a shot. So he filmed his own special. And handed it to the networks on a plate."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "A crash course in getting press and building links",
    "sUrl": "https://riseatseven.com/",
    "sText": "Rise at Seven",
    "tFront": "SEO",
    "tBack": "seo",
    "slug": "press",
    "img": "carrie",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Carrie Rose is the co-founder of Rise at Seven, a creative SEO agency. Over the last year I’ve been consistently blown away by how easy she makes getting press look. And it’s not press for press's sake. The reward is high quality backlinks which help her clients rank for ultra-competitive search terms."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "My guide to conversational copywriting",
    "sUrl": "https://www.towerpaddleboards.com/",
    "sText": "Tips",
    "tFront": "Copywriting",
    "tBack": "copywriting",
    "slug": "conversational",
    "img": "con",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Conversational copy is writing how you talk. No sales megaphone. No corporate drone. Just a conversation. But that's easier said than done. So I've put together this guide (packed with examples) to help teach you."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Using Unsplash for brand awareness and backlinks",
    "sUrl": "https://www.towerpaddleboards.com/",
    "sText": "Tower Paddle Boards",
    "tFront": "SEO",
    "tBack": "seo",
    "slug": "unsplash",
    "img": "un",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "One of my pals, Max, works for a paddleboard startup. They had some nice images from photoshoots. So he made an account on Unsplash (the photo discovery platform) and uploaded them. Five months later the images have 6M views. And 24k downloads."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Dave Gerhardt's 1 line sales email",
    "sUrl": "https://www.linkedin.com/in/davegerhardt/",
    "sText": "Dave Gerhardt",
    "tFront": "Sales",
    "tBack": "sales",
    "slug": "dave-gerhardt",
    "img": "dave",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Imagine you're trying to sell an exec coaching program. Here's the 1 line email Dave Gerhardt would send. The goal is simple. Get a reply. A reply gives you something to work with."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Real Marketing",
    "sUrl": "real-marketing",
    "sText": "A collection",
    "tFront": "Misc",
    "tBack": "misc",
    "slug": "real-marketing",
    "img": "pata",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Lifeless marketing is everywhere and we copy it without thinking. So I thought I'd share some examples of real stuff."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "How brands make friends on Twitter",
    "sUrl": "https://beamery.com/blog/personalized-emails",
    "sText": "Fast",
    "tFront": "Social Media",
    "tBack": "socialmedia",
    "slug": "fast",
    "img": "fast",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Fast coins term “Fastronaut”. Tweets “reply and we'll give your profile pic a Fastronaut helmet”"
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Growth Loops",
    "sUrl": "https://www.reforge.com/blog/growth-loops`",
    "sText": "Reforge",
    "tFront": "Viral",
    "tBack": "viral",
    "slug": "growth-loops",
    "img": "gl",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Most people think you build a product then you market it. Growth loops mean building the marketing into your product."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Ahrefs' Social Proof",
    "sUrl": "https://www.ahrefs.com",
    "sText": "Ahrefs",
    "tFront": "Conversion",
    "tBack": "conversion",
    "slug": "ahrefs-social-proof",
    "img": "asp",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "I love how Ahrefs does social proof. Different testimonials for different types of customer. People like seeing customers that look like them."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "How I promote my content",
    "sUrl": "https://www.marketingexamples.com",
    "sText": "Marketing Examples",
    "tFront": "Content",
    "tBack": "content",
    "slug": "sharing",
    "img": "paul",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "June 2019 I wrote my first marketing article. A year later my email list hit 19,000. No ads. No connections. No existing audience. The site grew because I learned how to promote my content on the internet. Here's my process."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "17 tips for great copywriting",
    "sUrl": "https://marketingexamples.com/copywriting",
    "sText": "A range",
    "tFront": "Copywriting",
    "tBack": "copywriting",
    "slug": "tips",
    "img": "ct",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "No filler. No wasted words. Only gold. Pound for pound the best copywriting article on the web. 17 copywriting tips. Put your feet up and enjoy."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "How Steve Jobs clarified Apple's message",
    "sUrl": "https://www.apple.com/",
    "sText": "Apple",
    "tFront": "Copywriting",
    "tBack": "copywriting",
    "slug": "think-different",
    "img": "steve",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "January 1983. Apple finish production of their latest computer, Lisa. Steve Jobs launches it with a nine-page ad in the New York Times. It's nine pages of geek speak. Nobody outside NASA is interested. Lisa sells just 10,000 units. Steve is fired from Apple."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Counterpunch like Carl",
    "sUrl": "https://www.instagram.com/beachbody",
    "sText": "Beachbody",
    "tFront": "Viral",
    "tBack": "viral",
    "slug": "counterpunch",
    "img": "cp",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "March 24. Popular Instagram account DudeWithSign takes aim at home workout videos. March 26. Beachbody’s CEO, Carl Daikeler, fires back, rallying his followers to post their home workouts with pride this Saturday."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "The most creative Coronavirus company pivots",
    "sUrl": "https://www.shakeshack.co.uk/",
    "sText": "Coronavirus",
    "tFront": "Viral",
    "tBack": "viral",
    "slug": "coronavirus-pivots",
    "img": "cv",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Evo Entertainment converted their parking lot into a drive-in movie theatre. Shake Shack launched “DIY burger kits” with a free cooking tutorial. New Balance switched production from shoes to masks."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Grubhub's link building strategy",
    "sUrl": "https://www.grubhub.com/",
    "sText": "Grubhub",
    "tFront": "SEO",
    "tBack": "seo",
    "slug": "grubhub-link-building",
    "img": "grubhub",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "How Grubhub's local link building strategy saw them generate 50% more organic traffic than their competitors in the online food delivery market"
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Chewy and the customer service multiplier",
    "sUrl": "https://www.chewy.com/",
    "sText": "Chewy",
    "tFront": "Customers",
    "tBack": "customers",
    "slug": "chewy",
    "img": "chewy",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Chewy's marketing strategy is simple: Delight customers and they’ll become life long customers. This article explains how Chewy's built a business around great customer service."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "How a creative Google ad got an investor's attention",
    "sUrl": "https://tadabase.io/",
    "sText": "Tadabase",
    "tFront": "PPC",
    "tBack": "ppc",
    "slug": "creative-google-ad",
    "img": "suster",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Tadabase's CEO, Moe Levine, was a long time admirer of investor, Mark Suster. So he set up some Google ads targeting Suster’s name, reminding him that he's yet to invest in no-code startups."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Surprising a customer with birthday cake",
    "sUrl": "https://www.lemonade.com/",
    "sText": "Lemonade",
    "tFront": "Customers",
    "tBack": "customers",
    "slug": "birthday-cake",
    "img": "lemon",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "It all started when Lemonade sent a personalised birthday email to loyal customer, Andrew. Andrew was touched and thanked them on Twitter."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "My favourite low-budget viral ads",
    "sUrl": "https://drafthouse.com/",
    "sText": "A collection",
    "tFront": "Ads",
    "tBack": "ads",
    "slug": "low-budget",
    "img": "fa",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "30 years ago, to get millions of views you needed a Super Bowl budget. Today all you need is a phone and an idea."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "The genius of no name's brand",
    "sUrl": "https://www.noname.ca/en_CA",
    "sText": "no name",
    "tFront": "Signalling",
    "tBack": "signalling",
    "slug": "no-name-brand",
    "img": "nn",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "no name is a “no nonsense, no frills” supermarket brand in Canada. Nothing special. A lot of supermarket brands share these “values”. The hard part is communicating them in a way that people remember."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "A story about my dad and PPC ads",
    "sUrl": "https://www.maximizeyourpotential.co.uk",
    "sText": "Maximize",
    "tFront": "PPC",
    "tBack": "ppc",
    "slug": "experiments",
    "img": "dad",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "My dad runs a small study skills company in the UK. It's an old-school business. Up until last year, the only marketing he's ever done was sending flyers to schools. But, over time, flyers had stopped working so well, so he started thinking about running digital ads."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "The marketing genius of Lil Nas X",
    "sUrl": "https://twitter.com/LilNasX?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor",
    "sText": "Lil Nas X",
    "tFront": "Viral",
    "tBack": "viral",
    "slug": "lil-nas-x",
    "img": "otr",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "This is the story of how Lil Nas X went from college dropout sleeping on his sister’s couch to breaking Mariah Carey’s record for the most consecutive weeks at No. 1 — in just seven months."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "The best word of mouth strategies in the world",
    "sUrl": "http://www.skipskitchen.com/",
    "sText": "Skip's Kitchen",
    "tFront": "Referral",
    "tBack": "referral",
    "slug": "word-of-mouth",
    "img": "skips",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Less than 1/1000 businesses have a proper word of mouth strategy. Yet they pull in customers just as reliably as paid ads for a fraction of the cost."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "How to write a landing page title",
    "sUrl": "https://refactoringui.com/book/",
    "sText": "Annie Maguire",
    "tFront": "Copywriting",
    "tBack": "copywriting",
    "slug": "landing-page-title",
    "img": "do",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Most things in marketing are unimportant. And we stress about them. Landing page headlines are important. And we don't stress about them. I've spent the past fortnight reading 500 landing page titles and talking to copywriting experts. This is what I've learnt:"
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Turning a restaurant robbery into a viral ad",
    "sUrl": "http://frijolesandfrescas.com/",
    "sText": "Frijoles & Frescas",
    "tFront": "Viral",
    "tBack": "viral",
    "slug": "taco-robbery",
    "img": "tacos",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "On the 16th December 2015 Frijoles & Frescas Tacos gets robbed. The next day, store owner, Greg Carlson, releases the security footage. Except he's added captions which turn the burglary into a story about how all the thieves wanted was their delicious tacos."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Refactoring UI: A lesson in high prices",
    "sUrl": "https://refactoringui.com/book/",
    "sText": "Refactoring UI",
    "tFront": "Pricing",
    "tBack": "pricing",
    "slug": "refactoring-ui",
    "img": "adam",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "How Adam Wathan and Steve Schoger escaped the dogma of e-book pricing and made $1.35M selling Refactoring UI, their design book."
  },
  {
    "num": "1",
    "title": "How I got 2,000 new subscribers from Product Hunt",
    "sUrl": "https://marketingexamples.com",
    "sText": "Marketing Examples",
    "tFront": "Conversion",
    "tBack": "conversion",
    "slug": "product-hunt",
    "img": "me",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Last Wednesday I launched Marketing Examples to Product Hunt. It received more than 1,500 upvotes, was voted Product of the Week, and my email list zoomed from 1,300 to 3,300 in the space of 72 hours. This is the step by step account of how I did it."
  },
  {
    "num": "1",
    "title": "How Nomad List dominates longer tail keywords",
    "sUrl": "https://nomadlist.com",
    "sText": "Nomad List",
    "tFront": "SEO",
    "tBack": "seo",
    "slug": "dominate-long-tail-keywords",
    "img": "nomad",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "A detailed case study explaining how Nomad List autogenerates several thousand indexed pages which hoover up organic traffic from long tail keyword phrases."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "The Indie Hackers newsletters",
    "sUrl": "https://indiehackers.com",
    "sText": "Indie Hackers",
    "tFront": "Email",
    "tBack": "email",
    "slug": "indie-hackers-newsletter",
    "img": "ih",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Indie Hackers is an online community of independent entrepreneurs, with a pretty sizeable email list. Throughout 2019 they’ve moved away from one generic email digest and started offering users the option of up to eight tailored newsletters"
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "The genius of Tesla's marketing strategy",
    "sUrl": "https://beamery.com/blog/personalized-emails",
    "sText": "Tesla",
    "tFront": "Referral",
    "tBack": "referral",
    "slug": "tesla-marketing-strategy",
    "img": "tesla",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Tesla have zero advertising budget. The focus is on turning customers into fans. The result is quite an extraordinary marketing strategy which I've broken down:"
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Let your customers write your copy for you",
    "sUrl": "https://www.designacademy.io/",
    "sText": "Design Academy",
    "tFront": "Copywriting",
    "tBack": "copywriting",
    "slug": "customers",
    "img": "da",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Copywriting doesn't require the “perfect line” or a “flash of inspiration”. Just talk to your customers, listen to what they're saying, and let them do the work for you. This article explains how Design Academy does just that"
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Using GIPHY for free brand awareness",
    "sUrl": "https://beamery.com/blog/personalized-emails",
    "sText": "Karla And Co.",
    "tFront": "Content",
    "tBack": "content",
    "slug": "giphy-marketing",
    "img": "giphy",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "All you need is a Giphy brand channel. Then any GIF you upload is publically available on Giphy's search engine. And there's nothing stopping you slipping in your logo, product, or even URL."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "How Rev. Chris grew 100k Instagram followers",
    "sUrl": "https://saintsaviours.net/",
    "sText": "Rev. Chris",
    "tFront": "Social Media",
    "tBack": "socialmedia",
    "slug": "rev-chris-instagram",
    "img": "revchris",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "For two and and a half years Rev. Chris Lee's Instagram account grew steadily. He posted mostly pictures of himself, his family, and the church. In July 2019 things changed. Chris started uploading “60 second sermons”."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "6 keys to sharing content on Twitter",
    "sUrl": "https://beamery.com/blog/personalized-emails",
    "sText": "Steph Smith",
    "tFront": "Content",
    "tBack": "content",
    "slug": "share-content-on-twitter",
    "img": "twitter",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "How you share is just as important as what you share. In one second someone subconsciously decides whether to engage with your content on Twitter or to scroll by. These tips are about optimising for that one second."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "How Volvo won the Super Bowl (without running an ad)",
    "sUrl": "https://beamery.com/blog/personalized-emails",
    "sText": "Volvo",
    "tFront": "Viral",
    "tBack": "viral",
    "slug": "volvo-contest",
    "img": "volvo",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "How Volvo's interception stole the show at the 2015 Super Bowl. Whenever you saw any other car commercial during the Super Bowl you could win a Volvo XC 60 for a loved one. All you had to do was was tweet why they deserved the car using the hashtag #VolvoContest during the commercial."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "7 practical ways to write copy that converts",
    "sUrl": "https://beamery.com/blog/personalized-emails",
    "sText": "Annie Maguire",
    "tFront": "Conversion",
    "tBack": "conversion",
    "slug": "copywriting",
    "img": "cc",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Conversion copywriting is an art. Here are 7 practical tips that you can implement today to make your landing page convert better."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "SEO project marketing",
    "sUrl": "https://kapwing.com",
    "sText": "Kapwing",
    "tFront": "SEO",
    "tBack": "seo",
    "slug": "seo-project-marketing",
    "img": "kapwing",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Make side projects. Host them on your own domain. Get them in front of the press. The idea is press exposure results in articles (and backlinks). And because the projects are hosted on your own domain any “link juice” flows to other pages on your website helping them rank better."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Podia's hub of competitor comparison pages",
    "sUrl": "https://podia.com",
    "sText": "Podia",
    "tFront": "SEO",
    "tBack": "seo",
    "slug": "competitor-comparison",
    "img": "podia",
    "imgType": "png",
    "desc": "How Podia built a hub of “[competitor] + alternative” pages pulling in 5,500 organic traffic each month"
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Basic SEO and Specsavers' FAQ page",
    "sUrl": "https://specsavers.com.au",
    "sText": "Specsavers",
    "tFront": "SEO",
    "tBack": "seo",
    "slug": "specsavers",
    "img": "up",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "The most common SEO mistake is relying on a single page website. Every new page is a new opportunity to target and rank for a search term. So if you’re dumping all your content on one page you’re limiting the number of search terms you can rank well for."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "CD Baby's confirmation email",
    "sUrl": "https://cdbaby.com/",
    "sText": "CD Baby",
    "tFront": "Referral",
    "tBack": "referral",
    "slug": "cd-baby-confirmation-email",
    "img": "cdbaby",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Back in 1998, when Derek Sivers first founded CD Baby, their order confirmation email was the regular: “Your order has shipped today. Please let us know if it doesn’t arrive. Thank you for your business.”"
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "How to get Tom Hanks on your podcast",
    "sUrl": "https://beamery.com/blog/personalized-emails",
    "sText": "The Nerdist Podcast",
    "tFront": "Signalling",
    "tBack": "signalling",
    "slug": "tom-hanks-podcast",
    "img": "tomhanks",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "This article explains how Chris Hardwick from the Nerdist podcast used a vintage 1934 Smith Corona typewriter to quite creatively bribe Tom Hanks onto the Nerdist podcast back in 2012."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "How to build a website which converts email subscribers",
    "sUrl": "https://marketingexamples.com",
    "sText": "Marketing Examples",
    "tFront": "Conversion",
    "tBack": "conversion",
    "slug": "email-subscribers",
    "img": "eoi",
    "imgType": "png",
    "desc": "12.9% of first time Marketing Examples users end up as a email subscribers. It's fair to say it's one of the best websites in the world at converting passers-by into email subscribers. This case study gives a step-by-step analysis."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "What to do if Joe Rogan recommends your product?",
    "sUrl": "https://www.iron-neck.com/",
    "sText": "Iron Neck",
    "tFront": "Social Media",
    "tBack": "socialmedia",
    "slug": "iron-neck",
    "img": "jr",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Iron Neck found themselves in the much sought after position of having Joe Rogan recommend their product. Well, they chopped up the footage into a video and ran ads targeting Joe's audience."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "The 1903 Tour de France",
    "sUrl": "https://www.letour.fr/en/",
    "sText": "L'Auto",
    "tFront": "Side Project",
    "tBack": "sideproject",
    "slug": "tour-de-france",
    "img": "tour",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "The 1903 Tour de France was set up as a “side project” which ended up changing the fortunes of its parent newspaper L'Auto"
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "Marketing tools are damaging your SEO. And how to fix it.",
    "sUrl": "https://www.todesktop.com/",
    "sText": "ToDesktop",
    "tFront": "SEO",
    "tBack": "seo",
    "slug": "performance",
    "img": "lighthouse",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "It's no secret that a site's “performance” is a ranking factor for search. But how does Google actually measure it? Well, open up Chrome DevTools, click the Audits tab, then Run Audits and you'll see that “Performance” is made up from 6 metrics"
  },
  {
    "num": "10",
    "title": "How to get 30,000 Hacker News visitors to your website",
    "sUrl": "https://simpleanalytics.com/",
    "sText": "Simple Analytics",
    "tFront": "Content",
    "tBack": "content",
    "slug": "drive-traffic-from-hacker-news",
    "img": "simpleanalytics",
    "imgType": "png",
    "desc": "How Adriaan van Rossum drove more than 30k visitors to his website from Hacker News"
  },
  {
    "num": "2",
    "title": "Why Notion's sign-up form converts so well",
    "sUrl": "http://notion.so",
    "sText": "Notion",
    "tFront": "Conversion",
    "tBack": "conversion",
    "slug": "sign-up-form-converts",
    "img": "notion",
    "imgType": "png",
    "desc": "In three years looking at landing pages, I’ve never come across a sign-up flow better at converting than Notions. Let’s get into it."
  },
  {
    "num": "1",
    "title": "How Jason Cohen does direct sales",
    "sUrl": "https://wpengine.com/",
    "sText": "WP Engine",
    "tFront": "Sales",
    "tBack": "sales",
    "slug": "jason-cohen-sales",
    "img": "wpengine",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "How Jason Cohen got his first 30 users before even building his product."
  },
  {
    "num": "1",
    "title": "How Jeff Johnson sold Nike's first shoes",
    "sUrl": "https://nike.com/",
    "sText": "Nike",
    "tFront": "Sales",
    "tBack": "sales",
    "slug": "how-nike-sold-first-shoes",
    "img": "nike",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "The story of how Phil Knight and Jeff Johnson drove to track meets all over the Pacific Northwest and sold more shoes than you can imagine out of the boots of their car."
  },
  {
    "num": "10",
    "title": "How Fortnite changed the way video games were marketed",
    "sUrl": "https://www.epicgames.com/fortnite",
    "sText": "Fortnite",
    "tFront": "Viral",
    "tBack": "viral",
    "slug": "fortnite-changed-marketing",
    "img": "fortnite",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "How Fortnite flipped the growth funnel on its head and forever changed the way video games are marketed."
  },
  {
    "num": "1",
    "title": "Reaching 3.7 million people posting canvases to YouTubers",
    "sUrl": "https://cryptic-tundra-74488.herokuapp.com/",
    "sText": "140 Canvas",
    "tFront": "Giveaway",
    "tBack": "giveaway",
    "slug": "youtube-marketing",
    "img": "140canvas",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "140 Canvas printed bespoke canvas', posted them to the PO boxes of YouTubers around the world and ended up with their product getting seen by over 3.7 million people."
  },
  {
    "num": "1",
    "title": "How step by step keyword research led to an SEO goldmine",
    "sUrl": "https://www.thomascook.com/holidays/weather/",
    "sText": "Thomas Cook",
    "tFront": "Seo",
    "tBack": "seo",
    "slug": "step-by-step-keyword-research",
    "img": "thomascook",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "How keyword research led Thomas Cook to an SEO goldmine and which pulls in an additional 450,000 organic users per month ..."
  },
  {
    "num": "1",
    "title": "A much improved newsletter sign up flow",
    "sUrl": "https://www.getrevue.co/",
    "sText": "Revue",
    "tFront": "Conversion",
    "tBack": "conversion",
    "slug": "newsletter-signup-flow",
    "img": "revue",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Asking to be added to your recipients' address book results in much improved email open rates"
  },
  {
    "num": "1",
    "title": "Costly Signalling Theory",
    "sUrl": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VYBOPPoiRRY",
    "sText": "Patreon",
    "tFront": "Signalling",
    "tBack": "signalling",
    "slug": "costly-signalling-theory",
    "img": "patreon",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "An awareness of costly signalling theory is invaluable in understanding the psychology of marketing."
  },
  {
    "num": "1",
    "title": "Becoming an antifragile brand. Ft. Lewis Capaldi & KFC",
    "sUrl": "https://www.kfc.co.uk/",
    "sText": "KFC",
    "tFront": "Viral",
    "tBack": "viral",
    "slug": "antifragile-brand",
    "img": "kfc",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "What Lewis Capaldi and KFC can teach you about becoming an antifragile brand."
  },
  {
    "num": "10",
    "title": "Growing 2.5 million subscribers piggybacking on viral trends",
    "sUrl": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UVxU2HzPGug",
    "sText": "Flare TV",
    "tFront": "Viral",
    "tBack": "viral",
    "slug": "piggyback-viral-trends",
    "img": "flaretv",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "How two 16 year old Canadian friends made several hundred thousand livestreaming the PewDiePie vs T-Series battle."
  },
  {
    "num": "1",
    "title": "How Tweet Photo designed virality into its product",
    "sUrl": "https://tweet.photo/",
    "sText": "Tweet Photo",
    "tFront": "Referral",
    "tBack": "referral",
    "slug": "design-virality-into-product",
    "img": "tweetphoto",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "How Tweet Photo grew from 0 to 1,700 users purely through organic referral."
  },
  {
    "num": "1",
    "title": "The key to self promotion on Reddit",
    "sUrl": "https://trennd.co/",
    "sText": "Trennd",
    "tFront": "Content",
    "tBack": "content",
    "slug": "self-promote-on-reddit",
    "img": "trennd",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Reddit is a bit of an untapped goldmine for marketers. The site is made up of thousands of niche communities (subreddits). This gives an opportunity to communicate directly with your audience."
  },
  {
    "num": "1",
    "title": "100 thank you cards. $5,200 extra revenue",
    "sUrl": "https://www.skinnywimpmoving.com/",
    "sText": "Skinny Wimp Moving Co.",
    "tFront": "Referral",
    "tBack": "referral",
    "slug": "thank-you-cards-promote-business",
    "img": "wimpy",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "How Mailing Out 100 Thank You Cards Earned Skinny Wimp Moving an extra $5,200 / mo"
  },
  {
    "num": "11",
    "title": "Serve a niche market. Get more attention",
    "sUrl": "https://yeezy.dating",
    "sText": "Yeezy Dating",
    "tFront": "Viral",
    "tBack": "viral",
    "slug": "serve-a-niche-market",
    "img": "yeezydating",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Why targeting a niche market was the key to the Yeezy Dating website going viral. A detailed analysis."
  },
  {
    "num": "7",
    "title": "Try writing “advice emails” instead of sales emails",
    "sUrl": "https://andco.life/",
    "sText": "AndCo",
    "tFront": "Cold Email",
    "tBack": "coldemail",
    "slug": "advice-emails",
    "img": "andco",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Why asking your leads for advice converts far better than directly trying to sell to them."
  },
  {
    "num": "6",
    "title": "How to write a funny cold email",
    "sUrl": "https://gusto.com/",
    "sText": "Gusto",
    "tFront": "Cold Email",
    "tBack": "coldemail",
    "slug": "funny-cold-email",
    "img": "gusto",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "How Gusto uses thier cute company dog to get your attention when cold emailing. A detailed case study on how to cold email"
  },
  {
    "num": "3",
    "title": "Use Intercom to build customer goodwill",
    "sUrl": "https://baremetrics.com",
    "sText": "Baremetrics",
    "tFront": "Conversion",
    "tBack": "conversion",
    "slug": "build-customer-goodwill",
    "img": "baremetrics",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "How technology could be leveraged creatively to build even tighter bonds with customers. A case study on Baremetrics use of Intercom."
  },
  {
    "num": "5",
    "title": "The “best sales email ever” from a personalised t-shirt company",
    "sUrl": "https://ramptshirts.com/",
    "sText": "Ramp T Shirts",
    "tFront": "Cold Email",
    "tBack": "coldemail",
    "slug": "best-sales-email-ever",
    "img": "rampt",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "How Ramp T Shirts managed to personalise 50,000 messages and ended up with of the most successful cold email campaigns of all time. A case study."
  },
  {
    "num": "2",
    "title": "How to build viral loops into your content marketing",
    "sUrl": "http://www.javascriptteacher.com/free-book.html",
    "sText": "Javascript Teacher",
    "tFront": "Referral",
    "tBack": "referral",
    "slug": "viral-loops-content-marketing",
    "img": "jstut",
    "imgType": "png",
    "desc": "How to leverage the power of retweets to build viral loops into your content marketing campaign. A case study about how Javascript Grammar eBook was shared around all over twitter"
  },
  {
    "num": "8",
    "title": "Understanding the power of signalling",
    "sUrl": "https://veed.io/",
    "sText": "Veed",
    "tFront": "Cold Email",
    "tBack": "coldemail",
    "slug": "signalling-in-marketing",
    "img": "veedstudio",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "Why extra effort and care in delivery of a message increases the perceived importance of that message"
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "How 2 minutes of personalisation transforms your cold emails",
    "sUrl": "https://beamery.com/blog/personalized-emails",
    "sText": "Beamery",
    "tFront": "Cold Email",
    "tBack": "coldemail",
    "slug": "write-personalised-cold-emails",
    "img": "beamery",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "An example from Beamery showing just how easy it is to personalise your cold emails without sounding like a jerk."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "How Joe Wicks started a movement",
    "sUrl": "https://www.thebodycoach.com/",
    "sText": "Joe Wicks",
    "tFront": "Viral",
    "tBack": "viral",
    "slug": "joe-wicks",
    "img": "jw",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "An example from Beamery showing just how easy it is to personalise your cold emails without sounding like a jerk."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "How Joe Ades sold potato peelers",
    "sUrl": "https://www.thebodycoach.com/",
    "sText": "Joe Ades",
    "tFront": "Sales",
    "tBack": "sales",
    "slug": "joe-ades",
    "img": "ja",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "An example from Beamery showing just how easy it is to personalise your cold emails without sounding like a jerk."
  },
  {
    "num": "9",
    "title": "“Michelin Guide” Marketing",
    "sUrl": "https://guide.michelin.com/gb/en",
    "sText": "Michelin",
    "tFront": "Content",
    "tBack": "content",
    "slug": "michelin-guide",
    "img": "michelin",
    "imgType": "jpg",
    "desc": "An old school content marketing story. France, 1900. Andre and Edouard Michelin had just started making tyres. The problem was there were less than 300 cars in France. So hoping to encourage car ownership they published the world's first “Michelin Guide”."
  }
]
